<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ficțiune on Site-ul comunității LEVEL</title>
    <link>https://candaparerevista.ro/tags/fic%C8%9Biune/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ficțiune on Site-ul comunității LEVEL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://candaparerevista.ro/tags/fic%C8%9Biune/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Children of Time</title>
      <link>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2023/05/carti-children-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2023/05/carti-children-of-time/</guid>
      <description>Error [RestateIntent]. It was a warning flag he had put in for himself, because he sometimes forgot what he was supposed to be accomplishing mid-code, leaving him with digital chimeras that did something entirely untoward. The system had detected part of the test design going off the rails and wanted him to redefine its goals. He began hunting through the nodes of the limited test environment to find out what had crashed. Error[RestateIntent]. ‘Yes, yes.’ Time to chalk up another failure and get some sleep. User[SenkoviD] Error[RestateIntent]. Just simple building blocks of system communication, the toys he used when he was building the virtual architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Night&#39;s Dawn</title>
      <link>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2023/01/carti-nights-dawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2023/01/carti-nights-dawn/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Did you know, the original ethnic Eskimos on Earth had several dozen words for snow&amp;rdquo;, Sinon said. &amp;ldquo;Really?&amp;rdquo; Choma answered from the other side of the winding ravine they were following. &amp;ldquo;Apparently so.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Excuse me for having my neural array assembled in too much of a hurry, but I don’t quite see the relevance to our current situation.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I just thought, it might be appropriate if we had an equal number of names for mud.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh right. Yes. Let’s see, we could have real crappy mud, bloody awful mud, pain in the ass mud, squeezes inside your exoskeleton and squelches a lot mud, and then there’s always the ultimate: drowning in mud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Killing Commendatore</title>
      <link>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2019/04/carti-killing-commendatore-triggerix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2019/04/carti-killing-commendatore-triggerix/</guid>
      <description>For everything around me was the product of connectivity. Nothing was absolute. Pain was a metaphor. All was relative. Light was shadow, shadow was light. I had no choice but to believe. What else could I do?
 Killing Commendatore, cel mai nou roman al lui Haruki Murakami, a fost publicat în Marea Britanie pe 9 octombrie 2018, la mai bine de un an de la apariția sa în Japonia. Primul lucru care mi-a atras atenția chiar dinainte să pun mâna pe carte a fost faptul că aceasta a fost interzisă în Hong Kong minorilor, fiind vândută doar sigilată și cu avertismente pe ambele coperte, considerată „indecentă”, însă nu mi se pare că iese din tipare din punctul acesta de vedere, având chiar mai puține scene explicite decât alte cărți de-ale lui.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1Q84</title>
      <link>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2019/04/carti-1q84-triggerix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://candaparerevista.ro/posts/2019/04/carti-1q84-triggerix/</guid>
      <description>After you do something like that, the everyday look of things might seem to change a little. Things may look different to you than they did before. But don&amp;rsquo;t let appearances fool you. There&amp;rsquo;s always only one reality.
 Acum câteva săptămâni am început 1Q84 de Haruki Murakami. Eram convinsă că o să-mi placă deoarece sunt mare fană a stilului lui și majoritatea romanelor pe care le-am citit m-au lăsat cu un sentiment asemănător pe care nu-l pot descrie. Murakami te întoarce când pe-o parte, când pe alta, îți insuflă o idee, iar apoi imediat după una contrară celei anterioare.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>